<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on IwéToyin</title>
    <link>https://iwetoyin.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on IwéToyin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iwetoyin.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why you should start a YouTube channel - Communication is key</title>
      <link>https://iwetoyin.netlify.app/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwetoyin.netlify.app/posts/post-1/</guid>
      
      <description>Hello hello, and welcome back my peopledem. I am back…again. If you are a first time reader then welcome to my humble abode! But if you have been following me on Instagram or Facebook (blast from the past I know) then you might be aware that I’ve started and restarted and renamed this blog of mine a few times. It’s gone through a few transitions in the last few years, but we are back again and here to stay for a while.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://iwetoyin.netlify.app/posts/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwetoyin.netlify.app/posts/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://iwetoyin.netlify.app/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwetoyin.netlify.app/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Hello and welcome to Ìwé Toyin! If you don&amp;rsquo;t already know, the handsome man in the pictures is me - the aforementioned Toyin (or Bait to some). So, just a little introduction. I&amp;rsquo;m a German-born, Nigerian, living in Birmingham and working as a Senior Software Engineer. Ìwé Toyin very loosely translates to Book of Toyin in Yoruba and that&amp;rsquo;s what this blog is. It&amp;rsquo;s a collection of my thoughts and feelings in written format.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
